Guide to the Second Aeon Archive 1967-1974 MSS.023
Fales Library and Special Collections
Second Aeon Archive
1967-1974
Fales Library and Special Collections
Second Aeon Publications
MSS.023
6.75 Linear Feet (14 boxes)
The Second Aeon Archive is comprised of all the correspondence and manuscript material that created Second Aeon's issues, such as: magazine layouts, page proofs, letters to the editor, illustration layouts, and original manuscripts.
Provenance
The Second Aeon Archive was acquired via purchase from Richard Aaron of Am Here Books, in 1974. The Second Aeon Archive is part of the Avant Garde Collection, collected at Fales Library during the 1960's and 70's by Mel Edelstein and Theodore Grieder.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Historical Note
Twenty-one issues of the magazine Second Aeon appeared between 1967 and 1974. It was published in Cardiff, Wales, with the support of the Welsh Arts Council and edited by Peter Finch. Containing poetry, short stories, cartoons, and illustrations, Second Aeon for it's period, was a comprehensive round up of the UK's small press activity. Noted contributors to the magazine included: Robert Bly, Gary Snyder, Allen Ginsberg, LeRoi Jones, Pablo Neruda, Charles Bukowski, Lorca, Octavio Paz, and countless others. In conjunction with the magazine, Second Aeon was also a small press that published poetry anthologies and books.
Scope and Content Note
The Second Aeon Archive is comprised of all the correspondence and manuscript material that created Second Aeon's issues, such as: magazine layouts, page proofs, letters to the editor, illustration layouts, and original manuscripts. Noted correspondents include Paul Auster, Carol Berg, Robert Bly, Charles Bukowski, William Burroughs, John Cage, Cyril Hodges, Alison Knowles, Jim Morrison, Jeff Nuttall, and Peter Redgrove. Also included in this collection are manuscripts used by Second Aeon's small press to publish various poetry books and anthologies.
Arrangement
Series I and III are arranged alphabetically and series 2 is arranged chronologically.
The collection is divided into three series: I) Correspondence to Peter Finch, editor II) Editorial Correspondence, 1967-1974, and III) Manuscripts.
Missing Title
Series I: Correspondence to Peter Finch, editor
Series II: Editorial Correspondence, 1967-1974
Series III, Subseries A: Manuscripts for Magazine Second Aeon
Series III, Subseries B: Manuscripts for Second Aeon's Small Press
Literature, Experimental.; English fiction |y 20th century.; Manuscripts for publication.; American fiction -- 20th century.; American poetry -- 20th century -- Periodicals; Avant-garde (Aesthetics); English poetry |y 20th century |v Periodicals.; English poetry |x Welsh authors |y 20th century |v Periodicals.; Correspondence.; Galley proofs.; Magazines (Periodicals); Scripts (documents); Aaron, Richard Emmet; Abse, Diane; Armstrong, Keith, 1946-; Aott, Keith, 1944-; Adler, Jeremy D.; Adlard, Peter; Andre, Michael; Ames, Terrence
- Series I: Correspondence to Peter Finch, editor
  Scope and Contents note
  Series I contains six boxes of correspondence to Peter Finch concerning the magazine Second Aeon. Noted correspondents include Paul Auster, Carol Berg, Robert Bly, Charles Bukowski, William Burroughs, John Cage, Cyril Hodges, Alison Knowles, Jim Morrison, Jeff Nuttall, and Peter Redgrove.
  - Correspondence from: Aaron, Richard; Abbott, Keith; Abse, Diane (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from: Adlard, Peter; Adler, Jeremy; Ames,Terence (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from: Anderson, Paul; Andre, Michael; Armstrong, Keith (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from: Armstrong, Michael; Ashbery, John; Atkinson-Jowett, George (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence from: Auster, Paul; Baller, S.T.; Bantock, Gavin (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence from: Barker, George; Barnett, Anthony; Bay, Martin (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence from: Beake, Fred; Bennett, John; Bennett, Roy (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from: Benveniste, Asa; Beresford, Anne; Berge, Carol (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence from: Berman, Ed; Berne, Stanley; Bielski, Alison (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence from: Birney, Earle; Black, David M.; Blazek, Douglas (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence from: Blish, James; Bly, Robert; Bockris, Victor (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence from: Bold, Alan; Bonard, Mary; Bontos, James (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence from: Booth, Felicity; Booth, Martin (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence from: Bosch, Manfred W., Bowles, Jerry G.; Branco, Joaquim (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence from: Breakwell, Ian; Brewer, Christine; Briers, David (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence from: Britt, Alan; Brown, Chris; Brown, Paul (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence from: Brown, Stew; Brownjohn, Alan; Buck, Paul (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence from: Bukowski, Charles; Burgis, Allan; Burns, Jim (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence from: Burns, Richard; Burroughs, William; Burrows, Miles (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence from: Bulter, Bill; Butles, Robert; Butterworth, Michael (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence from: Buttress, Derrick; Buzan, Tony; Cage, John (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence from: Cairncross, George; Calder, Dave; Callard, David (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence from: Cartland, Jeremy; Carvalno, Claudio Antonio; Casey, Gerard (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence from: Cash, Peter; Cassady, Carolyn; Cauble, Don (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence from: Chaloner, David; Charlton, Geoff; Chitlik, Paul (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence from: Chopin, Henri; Claire, Paula; Clark, Thomas A. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Correspondencefrom:Clavin,Hans;Cloves,Jeff;Cobbing,Bob (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence from: Conkie, Tommy; Cook, Geoffrey; Corman, Cid (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence from: Cope, Paul; Cotterell, Laurence; Cotton, John (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence from: Cox,William; Cozens, Andrew; Crab Grass Productions (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence from: Crowe, Kevin; Cunliffe, Dave; Curtis, Tony (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence from: Daly, Les; Damen; Herman; Dashi, Tony (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence from: Davies; Jeff; Davies, Wyn Islwyn; Davis, Norman H. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence from: Davis, Owen; DeFrance, Stephen; de Rook, G.J. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from: Dersley, Keith; Dewey, A.A.; DeWit, Andre (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from: Dixon, Steve; Dobbie, Mike; Donahue, Jack (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from: Dowden, George (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence from: Doyle, Mike; Drury, George D.; Dutton, Martin (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence from: Early, Tom; Edmonds, Marguerite; Ehrenberg, Felipe (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence from: Eisenstein, Samuel A. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from: England, Gerald; Enslin, Theodore; Eshleman, Clayton (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence from: Evans, Paul; Everette, Oliver; Fallon, Peter (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence from: Farrell, Deirdre; Faulkner, Peter; Fay, Kenneth (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence from: Feldman, Ruth; Finch, Peter; Finch, Vivienne; Finn, Andrea (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence from: Fisher, Allen; Fisher, Roy; Fleming, John (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence from: Fowler, Gene; Fox, Hugh; Fry, Colin (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence from: Fugard, Sheila; Fuller, Jean Overton; Fuller, Roy (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence from: Fulton, Len; Fulton, Robin; Furvinal, John (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence from: Galvin, Patrick N. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence from: Garlick, Raymond; Geller; Istvdn; Gerz, Jochen (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence from: Ghose, Amal; Gibbs, Michael; Ginsburg, Louis (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence from: Glen, Duncan; Gnazzo, Anthony J.; Gogady, Paul (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence from: Gogarty, Paul; Goldberg, Jeff; Golightly, Alan (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence from: Gordon, Giles; Gordon, James; Gotteman, Irving (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence from: Green, Jim (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence from: Green, Paul; Grieder, Theodore; Griffiths, Bryn (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence from: Groh, Klaus; Grubb, David; Gruffudd, Peter (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence from: Guest, Harry; Hacker, Marilyn; Hall, Donald (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence from: Hall, John; Hand, Alex; Harrison, Paul (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from: Harvey, Jon; Harwood, Lee; Hebron, Chris (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from: Hemensley, Kris; Herni, Adrian; Hepplewhite, Charles (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from: Hidden, Norman; Higgins, Dick; Hill, A.G. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence from: Hilton, Jeremy; Hirschman, Jack (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence from: Hodges, Cyril (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence from: Hodges, Cyril (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from: Hodges, Cyril (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence from: Hoida, Peter; Holbrook, David; Holland, Geoff (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence from: Hollis, Ena; Holmes, Philip; Horder, John (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence from: Horovitz, Frances; Horoviytz, Michael; Houeclard, Dom Sylvester (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence from: Hughes, D.; Hughes, Vaughan; Ireland, Alan (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence from: Jackowska, Nicki; Jackson, Alan; Jackson, N.S. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence from: Jaffin, David; James, John; Jarman, Geraint (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence from: Jay, Peter; Jenkins, Nigel; Jenkins, Philip (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence from: Jenkins, Tom; Johnson, B.S., Johnson, John (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence from: Jones, John Idris; Jones, Rae Desmond; Jones, Tomma (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence from: Joris, Pierre; Karoly, Halasz; Kelly, Bernard (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from: Kernagham, Alex; Kingham, Terry C., Klimo, Jan (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from: Knowles, Alison Kostelanetz, Richard; Kruss, Tom (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from: Land, Thomas; Lange; Gerald; LaSalle, Richard (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence from: Laughlin, James; Lee, Joan; Legman, G. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence from: Leighton, Bob; Levi, Peter; Lewis-Smith, Anne (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence from: Lloyd, Andrew; Lloyd, Robin; Locke, Duane (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from: Long, Don; Longville, Tim; Loose, Gerry (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence from: Lopez, Tony; Lowe, Derek; Lucie-Smith, Edward (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence from: Lykiard, Alexis, MacBeth, George, McBride, Dick (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence from: McBride, John; McCarthy, Cavan; McCarthy, Ulli (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence from: Machado, Antonio; McManus, Peter; MacSweeney, Barry (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence from: Magee, Nes; Mammatt, D.R.; Mangelsdorff, Rich (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence from: Mariah, Paul; Markham, K.A.; Marshfield, Alan (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence from: Mathews, Paul; Mathews, Richard; Mathias, Roland (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence from: Matthias, John; Mayer, Peter; Mercer, David (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence from: Michel, Julian G.; Miller, Brown, Miller, Richard (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence from: Mills, Stuart; Mitchell, Adrian; Mitchell, Roger (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence from: Montag, Tom; Montgomery, John; Morgan, Christopher (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence from: Morgan, Edwin; Morgan, Peter (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence from: Morris, Stephen (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence from: Morrison, Jim; Moser, Norm; Mottram, Eric (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence from: Musgrave, Susan; Nannucci, Maurizio; Nations, Opal (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence from: niikuni, Seiichi; Nijmeijer, Peter; Noyce, John (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence from: Nuttall, Jeff; Oppenheimer, Joel; Orridge, Genesis P. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from: Osborne, John; Osinski, Franklin W.W.; Ourini, Victor (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from: Oxley, William; Pacey, Phillip (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from: Parfitt, Will (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence from: Parr, Malcolm; Patten, Brian; Paul, Jay S. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence from: Pedersen, L.D.; Perrie, Walter; Perry, Alan (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence from: Petarel, Martin, Phillips, L.C.; Phillips, Tom (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from: Pickard, Bill; Pilcher, Barry Edgar (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence from: Plymell, Charlie; Porter, Peter; Price, David Watkin (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence from: Price, Ken; Radd, David; Radin, Betty (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence from: Randall, Elaine; Ratcliffe, Eric; Raworth, Tom (Box 5)
  - Correspondence from: Regrove, Peter; Reeves, Trevor (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence from: Rice, John; Rickaby, Tony; Riddell, Alan (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence from: Riley, John; Riley, Peter; Ritchies, Malcolm (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence from: Robinson, Ian; Robinson, John; Robson, Andy (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence from: Roche, Paul; Rowan, J.; Rudolf, Anthony (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence from: Russell, Dick; Russell, Ray; Schmitz, Jacques L. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence from: Schwenk, Norman; Sergeant, Howard; Sharkey, John (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence from: Shields, Mike; Shingleton, Peter; Shuttle, Peter (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence from: Simpson, Matt; Sinchair, Jain; Sneyd, Steve (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence from: Sobin, A.G.; Sorcic, Jim Orvino; Sowerby, J.K. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence from: Spiro, Leon; Spratling, Neil; Srinivas, Krishna (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence from: Stayner, Scott; Steane, Nina; Swann, Brian (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence from: Swiss, Thom; Szostek, J.H.; Taylor, Kent (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence from: Taylor, Sam; Teague, Andrew; Telling, Derek (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence from: Thenior, Ralf; Thomas, Don; Thomas, D.M. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from: Thomas, G.; Thomas, Ronald Stuart; Tidler, Charles (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from: Tipton, David; Toczek, Nick; Torrance, Chris (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from: Tremallen, Dave (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence from: Tripp, John; Turnbull, Gael; Upton, Lawrence (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence from: Urin, Victor; Valoch, Jiri; Verey, Charles (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence from: Viewpoint Magazine; Vimal, G.P.; Von Tersch, Gary (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence from: Wade, David; Wade, John Stevens; Wagner, D.; Wain, John (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence from: Wake, Brian (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence from: Walsh, J.A. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence from: Waintiling, William (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence from: Ward, J.P.; Ward, Philip; Watts, Richard (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence from: Weaver, Roger; Webb, Harri; Weinstein, Norman (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence from: Welsh Arts Council (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence from: Whalen, Philip; Williams, Brian; Williams, Clive (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence from: Williams, Jonathan; Winans, Al; Wisker, Alistair (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence from: Wright, Meg; Wyatt, Bill; Yates, Rowdy (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence from: Zugbrugg, Nicholas (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Series II: Editorial Correspondence, 1967-1974
  Series II contains four boxes of correspondence to Peter Finch pertaining to editorial concerns of the magazines uch as: subscription requests, poetry admissions, thank you/congratulatory notes, and other such solicitations. This series also includes Peter Finch's personal correspondence comprising a copybook and letters dealing with his career as a poet.
  - Correspondence from: A-Z, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from: A-Z, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from:A-K, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence L-Z, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: A-L, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: M-Z, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: A-L, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from: M-Z, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from: A-C, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence D-G:, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence H-M:, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence N-Z:, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence A-C:, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence D-N:, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence O-Z:, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence A-M:, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence N-Z:, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Undated, A-G, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Undated, H-R, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Undated, S-Z, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from: Finch, Peter, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Personal: A-D (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Personal, E-S (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Personal, T-Z (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Personal, Unidentified (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Pink Peace (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Series III: Subseries A: Manuscripts for magazine Second Aeon
  - Archive lists and inventory (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Advertising brochures (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Issue no. 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript materials: Issues No. 8 and 9 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript materials: Issue No. 11 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript materials: Issue No. 12 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript materials: Isue No. 13 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Manucript materials: Issue No. 14 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript materials: Issue No. 15 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Page proofs: Issue No. 15 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript materials: Issues No. 16 and 17 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Page proofs: Issues No. 16 and 17 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Illustration Mockups: Issue No. 16? (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Cover Mockup: Issue No. 18 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript materials: Issue No. 18 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Page proofs: Issue No. 18 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Mockup: Issue No. 18 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript: Issues Nos. 19-21 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript: Issues Nos. 19-21 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Visuals: Issues Nos. 19-21 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Unpublished manuscripts (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Unpublished unsigned manuscripts (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Series III: Subseries B: Manuscripts for Second Aeon's small press
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Bantock, Gavin (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Blazek, Douglas; Booth, Martin; Brown, Paul (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Burns, Jim; Callard, David (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Clark, Tom; Dowden, George; Finch, Peter (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Finch, Peter (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Hodges, Cyril (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Jenkins, Philip; Kryss, Tom (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Lloyd, Andrew (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Lykiard, Alexis (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Morgan, Christopher (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Morgan, Huw (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Morris, Stephen (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Parfitt, Will (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section:Redgrove, Peter; Sharkey, John (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Taylor, Kent; Tipton, David (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Thomas, D.M. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Tripp, John (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Tripp, John (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Tripp, John (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Von Tersch, Gary (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Wake, Brian (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Wantling, William (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Wantling, William (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Manuscript and correspondence, book section: Ward, John P. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - No Walls Broadsheet: Nos. 1, 4-9, 12-18Manuscript and correspondence, book section: (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - No Walls Broadsheet: manuscripts (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - No Walls Broadsheet: mockups (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Anthology Book Section: Diamonds in the Dust: The Cardiff Poets, ed. Peter Finch (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Anthology Book Section: For Jack Kerouac Poems on Death, ed. Peter Finch (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Anthology Book Section: Found Poems, ed. Malcolm Parr (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Anthology Book Section: Rumpus, ed. Christopher Morgan (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Anthology Book Section: A Storm of Blood, ed. Peter Finch (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Anthology Book Section: Traveling Circus Sampler, ed. Peter Finch (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Anthology Book Section: Typewriter Poems, ed. Peter Finch (Box 14, Folder 7)